# PABLO MARTIN, LOPEZ



## About me

I want to acquire experience and skills that allow me to grow and continue developing knowledge. Manage to face new challenges by demonstrating my potential, in order to achieve proposed goals in the medium and long term.



+54 1165428432



pablo\_mtv08@hotmail.com



Argentina - Buenos Aires

Age: 30

## **LANGUAGES**

- Native Spanish
- Intermediate English

## **NETWORKS/WEB**



github.com/pabloApoca



<u>|linkedin.com/in/pablo-martin-lopez/</u>



**XINUX** 

pabloapoca.github.io/mi-portfolio/

## **OPERATING SYSTEMS**

WINDOWS

100 %

## Full Stack Developer

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **Digital House**

Jan 2024 - Present

## **Programming Professor at GO**

Professor and content creator for the Digital House Certified Tech Developer program.

Technologies: Go / GinGonic / Web Services API / MySQL

### **TECNOSOFTWARE**

Jan 2024 - Present

## Ssr Software Developer at Prisma Medios de Pagos

I work on the development of Software for banking systems regarding Banelco ATMs.

Technologies: Html / Css / Tailwind CSS / Bootstrap / Javascript / Git-Bitbucket / Jira / Scrum / Teams.

## OverVision Analytics

Apr 2022 - Oct 2023

## Full Stack Developer

Development of Desktop and Mobile applications.

Technologies: PHP / Laravel 9, VueJs 3 / Html / Css / Tailwind CSS / Javascript, Databases PostgreSQL, Git-GitLab y Jira.

## <u>Digital House</u>

Mar 2021- Jul 2023

## **BackEnd Programming Technician**

- Mar 2021 Apr 2022 (FULLTIME): Teaching Backend programming classes in Mercadolibre and Globant Bootcamps, technologies: Git, Java +11, Golang, Api/Rest Spring Boot, Testing, Databases SQL/NoSQL and Scrum methodology.
- <u>Apr 2022 Jul 2023 (PART TIME)</u>: Technical Assistant and content designer in the Digital House career, Certified Tech Developer, together with <u>Mercadolibre</u> and <u>Globant</u> participating in the second year with the Java programming language and third year in Golang.

## Certant

Oct 2020 - Mar 2021

## **Full Stack Developer**

Requirements analysis, Software development in Java programming language, web development with Angular Javascript Framework and developing SQL queries in MySQL.

## **EDUCATION**

## School of Technical Education N° 3 - Claypole

2009 - 2011

- Bachelor's Degree in Production of Goods and Services.
- Senior Master of Works.

## National University of Lanús - <u>UNLA</u>

2012-2021

Career: Bachelor's degree in systems

- University Programmer Analyst (Completed).
- Bachelor's degree in systems (In progress, I only need the Thesis)

## **SKILLS**

Java / PHP / Go / Spring Boot / Angular +13 / VueJs 3
HTML 5 / CSS 3 / Javascript / Boostrap / Tailwind CSS
Api Rest / Databases SQL-noSQL / Scrum / Jira / Git / Postman

## PABLO MARTIN, LOPEZ

## Desarrollador Full Stack

## **EXPERIENCIA**

## **Digital House**

Ene 2024 - Actualidad

## Profesor de Programación en GO

Profesor y contenidista en la carrera de Digital House Certified Tech Developer.

Tecnologías: Go / GinGonic / Web Services API / MySQL

### **TECNOSOFTWARE**

Ene 2024 - Actualidad

## Ssr Software Developer en Prisma Medios de Pagos

Trabajo en el desarrollo de Software para los sistemas bancarios con respecto a los cajeros Banelco.

Tecnologías: Html / Css / Tailwind CSS / Bootstrap / Javascript / Git-Bitbucket / Jira / Scrum / Teams.

## **OverVision Analytics**

Abr 2022 - Oct 2023

**Desarrollador Full Stack** 

Desarrollo de aplicaciones de Escritorio y Mobile. Tecnologías: PHP / Laravel 9, VueJs 3 / Html / Css / Tailwind CSS / Javascript, Base de datos PostgreSQL, Git-GitLab y Jira.

## **Digital House**

Mar 2021- Jul 2023

## Técnico de Programación BackEnd

- Mar 2021 Abr 2022 (FULLTIME): Dictado de clases de programación Backend en Bootcamps de Mercadolibre y Globant, tecnologías: Git, Java +11, Golang, Api/Rest Spring Boot, Testing, Bases de datos SQL/NoSQL y metodología Scrum.
- Abr 2022 Jul 2023 (PART TIME): Asistente Técnico y contenidista en la carrera de Digital House, Certified Tech Developer, junto a Mercadolibre y Globant participando en el segundo año con el lenguaje de programación Java y tercer año en Golang.

#### Certant

Oct 2020 - Mar 2021

## **Desarrollador Full Stack**

Análisis de requerimientos, desarrollo de Software en lenguaje de programación Java, desarrollo web con Framework de Javascript Angular y desarrollar queries sql en MySQL.

## **FORMACIÓN**

## Escuela de Educación Técnica Nº 3 - Claypole

2009 - 2011

- Bachillerato en Producción de Bienes y Servicios
- Técnico Maestro Mayor de Obras.

## Universidad Nacional de Lanús - UNLA

2012-2021

Carrera: Licenciatura en sistemas

- Analista Programador Universitario (Completado).
- Licenciatura en sistemas (En curso, solo me falta la Tesis).

## **SKILLS**

Java / PHP / Go / Spring Boot / Angular +13 / VueJs 3 HTML 5 / CSS 3 / Javascript / Boostrap / Tailwind CSS Api Rest / Databases SQL-noSQL / Scrum / Jira / Git / Postman



## Sobre mi

Deseo adquirir experiencia y aptitudes que me permitan crecer y seguir desarrollando conocimientos. Lograr enfrentar nuevos desafíos demostrando mi potencial, con el fin de alcanzar metas propuestas a mediano y largo plazo.



+54 1165428432



pablo\_mtv08@hotmail.com



Buenos Aires - Argentina

Edad: 30

#### **IDIOMAS**

- Español (Nativo)
- Ingles (Intermedio)

## REDES/WEB



<u>github.com/pabloApoca</u>



linkedin.com/in/pablo-martin-lopez/



pabloapoca.github.io/mi-portfolio/

## SISTEMAS OPERATIVOS

**MINDOWS** 100 % 50 %

**XINUX**